Kenneth Hazen Aynesworth papers, Inclusive: 1826-1965, undated, Bulk: 1930-1943
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Correspondence, 1898-1944, undated; 2
  - Received, 1899-1944, undated; 1; This subseries contains fourteen document boxes.
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 August 23- September 9 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 September 14- October 16 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 October 18- November 10 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 November 16-20 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 November 24-30 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 December 3-15 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 December 17-31 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1944 January (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1944 February 1-7 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (1 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (2 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (3 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (4 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (5 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (6 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (7 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (8 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General (9 of 9), undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Sent, 1898-1944, undated; 2; The subseries consists of ten document boxes.
    The following series is comprised of correspondence that Kenneth Aynesworth sent to friends and co-workers. The series is organized alphabetically by the last name of the individual to whom Aynesworth was writing. The materials are in average to good condition.
    The folders are organized alphabetically by the last name of the individual to whom Aynesworth had sent the letter.
    - Abeel-Abney, 1931-1939 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Academy-Aerl, 1937-1941 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Aetna-Albaugh, 1930-1943 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Alcalde-Alford, 1930-1943 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Allred-Alvarez, 1934-1942 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - American Central Life- American College of Surgeons, 1930-1943 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - American Cystoscope- American Journal, 1931-1942 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - American Medical Association, 1934-1937 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - American Medical Association, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - American Medical Association, 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - American Medical Colleges-Andronis, 1930-1941 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Annals-Asbury, 1931-1943 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Associated-Azbelle, 1932-1943 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Baer-Bailey, Clyde, 1930-1940 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Bailey, Ralph-Barker, 1931-1943 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Barnard-Batton, 1929-1943 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Bausch-Bell, 1929-1938 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Benedict-Berry, 1930-1943 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Bethel-Blackwood, 1930-1943 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Blair-Bower, 1930-1943 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Bradford-Brian, 1930-1940 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Briggs-Brooks, Barney, 1931-1942 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Brooks, Samuel-Brown, George, 1929-1942 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Brown, J.J.-Brown, Marion, 1934-1940 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Brown, William-Buchanan, 1930-1943 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Buck, 1930-1938 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Buckingham-Buie, 1936-1940 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Bullock-Burgin, 1937-1941 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Burleson-Burt, 1934-1940 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Bush-Byrum, 1930-1939 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Caddell-Campbell, C.L., 1935-1943 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Campbell, Willis-Carney, 1930-1941 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Carolina-Carrington, 1935-1943 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Carroll, Charles, 1933-1936 February (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Carroll, Charles, 1936 May-1940 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Carson-Caviness, 1932-1942 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Central-Chansler, 1931-1941 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Charlton-Clark, 1929-1943 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Clarke-Clifton, Albert, 1937-1939 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Clifton, R.A., 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Clifton, R.A., 1934-1939 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Clifton, Truitt-Cole, 1930-1940 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Colgin-Collom, 1932-1942 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Colp-Connally, E.L., 1931-1943 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Connally, Tom, 1933-1941 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Connors-Craig, 1932-1944 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Crane-Crile, 1930-1941 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Crimmins-Cromeans, 1933-1943 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Cross, O.H., 1931-1941 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Crosthwait-Curtis, 1931-1943 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Dallas-Dauber, 1930-1943 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Daughtry-Davis, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Dawson-Del Rio, 1931-1943 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - DeMarrs-Dewey, 1931-1941 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Diamond-Dohoney, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Dolley-Doughtie, 1934-1943 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dowdle-Dupree, 1933-1944 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Easterling-Elliott, 1930-1943 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Ellis-Exclusive, 1931-1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Faiman-Faulkner, 1937-1944 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Favrot-Ferguson, L.K., 1931-1941 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Ferguson, Miriam, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Fewell-Fitzhugh, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Fitzpatrick-Ford, 1930-1943 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Fort-Foster, 1931-1940 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Fowler-Funderburk, 1931-1943 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Gaeke-Gamble, 1931-1942 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Gambrell-Gammel, 1930-1936 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Gants-Gay, 1930-1943 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Gayle-Geiser, 1932-1942 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - General-Gilmore, 1929-1943 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Glass-Goodall, 1934-1941 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Goode-Graves, 1932-1940 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Gray-Greenwood, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Greer-Guthe, 1930-1943 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Hackett-Hall, 1934-1942 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Halze-Hardin, 1930-1940 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Hardy-Harpers, 1934-1940 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Harrington-Harris, Merton, 1931-1941 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Harris, Titus-Harrison, Guy, 1932-1942 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Harrison, J.P.-Hendricks, 1929-1942 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Henson-Heyd, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Hickman, C.F.-Hickman, J.E., 1932-1941 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hickman, Lawrence-Hicks, 1936-1941 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Hill-Hodges, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Hoeber-Holstead, 1929-1941 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Holt-Houghton, 1932-1943 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Houston-Howes, 1931-1941 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Huchingson-Hutcheson, 1932-1942 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Industrial-Institute, 1930-1943 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Interior-Interne, 1933-1943 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Jackson-Jensen, 1931-1942 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Jester-Johnson, 1935-1942 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Jolly-Juhl, 1936-1943 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Kantor-Kleinberg, 1929-1942 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Knight-Kyle, 1930-1943 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Lacy-Lamar, 1932-1938 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Lampe-Larkin, 1937-1941 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Latham-Lincoln, 1931-1939 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Lippincott-Lispcomb, 1937-1943 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Lipshutz-Lovelace, Carl, 1930-1941 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Lovelace, J.D.-Lyons, 1929-1940 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mack-Majors, 1930-1942 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Male-Marcus, 1930-1939 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Marquez-Mason, 1931-1943 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Massey-Matlock, J.D., 1933-1939 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Matlock, John, 1929-1941 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Matlock, Joseph-McClellan, 1931-1943 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - McClure-McCraw, 1933-1943 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - McCullough-McDowell, 1932-1940 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - McGehee-McMahan, 1932-1944 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - McMechan-Media, 1931-1941 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Medical-Mercer, 1933-1943 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Meroney-Migel, 1932-1940 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Milam-Milling, 1930-1943 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Mitchell, 1931-1943 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Mobley-Moody, 1929-1943 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Moore-Morgan, 1931-1941 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Morley-Moursund, 1932-1942 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Mueller-Myrick, 1931-1942 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Nabors-National, 1931-1943 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Nau-Neff, 1931-1942 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Neighbors-Nunnelly, 1930-1943 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Ochsner, Alton, 1934-1943 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - O’Daniel-O’Donnell, 1938-1943 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Ogilvie-Owens, 1930-1943 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pacific-Parker, 1930-1940 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Parks-Paul, 1935-1939 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Payne-Pearce, 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Pearson-Phelps, 1930-1942 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Phillips-Pilling, 1931-1941 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Pillot, 1942-1943 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Pittillo-Pukluda, 1931-1940 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Pope-Price, 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Pridgen-Quebe, 1930-1943 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Rainey-Randall, 1930-1942 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Rankin-Reinke, 1931-1943 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Rembert-Riley, 1930-1943 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Rischar-Roberts, 1933-1942 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Robey-Rotan, 1931-1943 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Rouse-Russ, 1929-1943 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Russell, F.B., 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Russell, Lillian-Ryan, 1930-1943 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Sachs-Sanders, 1934-1942 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Sanford-Schreier, 1929-1943 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Schuler-Scoffield, 1932-1943 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Scott-Seaton, O.A., 1933-1943 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Seaton, R.A.-Sherman, 1929-1943 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Shettles-Sigerest, 1931-1943 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Silvers-Sims, 1932-1943 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Singleton, Albert, 1931-1940 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Singleton, Gordon-Smith, G.R., 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Smith, Howard-Snyder, 1930-1942 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Somervell-Spies, 1930-1944 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Springer-Stark, 1930-1940 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - State- Stephenson, 1930-1943 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Stolte-Summers, 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Surgeon-Swift, 1933-1942 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Tabb-Taylor, Bruce, 1930-1942 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Taylor, Holman-Temple, 1934-1941 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Tennessee-Teolin, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Terrill-Thomas, 1931-1943 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Thompson-Torbett, 1931-1942 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Torrence-Trippet, 1931-1940 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Trout-Tyrone, 1929-1943 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Ullrich-United, 1930-1943 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Ursula-Utilities, 1935-1939 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Utitz, J.J., 1935-1940 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Utitz, J.J., 1941-1943 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Vahrenkamp-Votaw, 1930-1943 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Waco-Walker, 1929-1942 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Wangensteen-Watts, 1929-1940 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Wear-Weaver, 1930-1934 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Webb-Wecter, 1930-1941 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Wedemeyer-Welton, 1931-1943 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Wernik-Whitaker, 1931-1943 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - White-Who’s, 1935-1943 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Whom, 1930-1936 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Whom, 1937-1941 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Whom, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Whom, 1943-1944 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Widdecke-Wilkes, 1930-1943 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Williams, 1930-1941 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Williamson-Wilson, 1933-1943 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Wiltsie-Wolfe, 1929-1942 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Wood, A.-Wood, Eugene, 1898-1933 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Wood, Mittie-Wright, 1931-1944 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Yancey, E.F., 1930-1935 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Yancey, Robert-Young, 1931-1938 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Zabre-Zoning, 1932-1944 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Cards and Announcements, 1904-1943, undated; 3; This subseries is comprised of one document box.
    The following subseries contains greeting cards, Christmas cards, announcements, wedding invitations, graduation invitations, and tickets stubs collected by Dr. Aynesworth. The materials are in good condition.
    The folders are organized alphabetically according to type of material.
    - Announcements, 1932-1943 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Announcements, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Christmas, 1937-1942 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Christmas (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Christmas (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Christmas (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Invitations, 1904-1942 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Memorandums: Thank Yous, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Tickets: Admission, 1933-1939, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Philosopher's Club, 1930-1944, undated; 4; This subseries contains two document boxes.
    General condition: Good.
    This subseries contains correspondence that Dr. Aynesworth exchanged with fellow members of the Philosopher's Club, an organization created in appreciation of various historical philosophers. The materials are in good condition.
    Due to the small nature of the subseries, the materials are organized chronologically.
    - General, 1930-1933 April (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - General, 1933 May-December (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - General, 1934 January-May (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - General, 1934 August-December (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - General, 1935 January-May (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - General, 1935 July-1936 February (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - General, 1936 March-December (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - General, 1937-1938 March (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - General, 1938 April-1939 March (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - General, 1939 April-December (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - General, 1940 January-October (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - General, 1940 November-1941 December (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - General, 1942 January-October (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - General, 1942 November-1943 September (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - General, 1943 October-1944 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - General, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Baylor University, 1929-1943, undated; 5; This subseries is housed in one document box.
    This subseries contains correspondence exchanged between Dr. Kenneth Aynesworth and Baylor University officials. Noticeably absent from the materials are letters from Aynesworth's time at Baylor as a student and correspondence pertaining to his initial gift which became The Texas Collection. The materials are in good condition.
    - General, 1929- 1931 March (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - General, 1931 June- 1933 May (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - General, 1933 June- July (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - General, 1933 August- November (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - General, 1934 January (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - General, 1934 March-July (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - General, 1934 October 6-17 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - General, 1935 October 21- 1936 April 7 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - General, 1936 April 25- September (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - General, 1936 October- 1937 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - General, 1938-1939 June (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - General, 1939 August- December (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - General, 1940 February- November (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - General, 1940 December- 1941 October (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - General, 1941 November-December (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - General, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - General, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Photographic Materials, 1937-1944, undated; 3
  This series contains photographs and tintypes pertaining to the Aynesworth family. There is also a folder of photographs concerning World War II England, one of Aynesworth's sons was a veteran of the European theater. These materials are in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print; Tintypes
  - Photographs: General, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: General (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: General (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Aynesworth Family, 1943, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: England: Wartime, circa 1940s (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Kenneth Aynesworth (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Kenneth Aynesworth (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Tintypes: General, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Medical Practice, 1929-1943, undated; 4
  This series contains medical records from Dr. Aynesworth's practice in the Waco area. Materials pertaining to the Central Texas Clinic, Hillcrest Hospital, Providence Hospital, and Providence Sanitarium can be found in this series. The materials are in good condition.
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1929 November (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1929 November- December (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1930 January-July (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1930 August-1931 March (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1931 April-November (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1931 December-1932 March (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1932 April-November (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Central Texas Clinic, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Hillcrest Hospital, 1939-1941 July (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Hillcrest Hospital, 1941 August- 1943, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Providence Hospital, 1938-1943 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Providence Sanitarium: General, 1930-1940 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Providence Sanitarium: General, 1941-1942 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Providence Sanitarium: General, 1942, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Providence Sanitarium: Book Donation: Kenneth Hazen Aynesworth, 1933 February 9 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Slides: X-rays (1 of 3), undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Slides: X-rays (2 of 3), undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Slides: X-rays (3 of 3), undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Subject Files, 1898-1944, undated; 5
  Dr. Aynesworth was an avid collector of local and state history. This series contain subject files pertaining to various topics of interest including education, Baylor University, politics, medicine, Texas, Waco, and World War II. The materials are in average to good condition.
  - Book Lists, 1943, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Communism, 1931-1937, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Education: General, 1929-1930 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Education: General, 1931-1932 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Education: General, 1933-1935 February (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Education: General, 1935 October- 1936 June (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Education: General, 1936 November (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Education: General, 1937-1939 June (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Education: General, 1939 October-1941 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Education: General, 1943, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Education: General, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Baylor University, 1930-1931 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Baylor University, 1933 April-May (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Baylor University, 1933 June-1934 April (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Baylor University, 1934 May-August (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Baylor University, 1935-1936 May (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Baylor University, 1936 June-August (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Baylor University, 1936 November-1937 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Baylor University, 1939-1940 May (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Baylor University, 1940 June-November (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Baylor University, 1941-1942, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Franklin Roosevelt: Third Term (1 of 2), 1940 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Franklin Roosevelt: Third Term (2 of 2), 1940 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Medicine, 1930-1935 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Medicine, 1936-1937 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Medicine, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Medicine, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Medicine, 1940-1941 August (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Medicine, 1941 October- 1942 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Subject Files: Medicine, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Medicine (1 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Medicine (2 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Medicine (3 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Politics: General, 1929-1940 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Politics: General, 1941-1942 April (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Politics: General, 1942 July-1943 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Politics: General, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Politics: Campaign Bulletins, 1933-1936 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Politics: Campaign Bulletins, 1940-1942 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Politics: Campaign Bulletins (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Politics: Campaign Bulletins (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Politics: New Deal, circa 1930s (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Texas, 1928-1936 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Texas, 1937-1940 September (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Texas, 1940 November-1941 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Texas, 1942-1943, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Texas (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Texas (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - The Texas Collection: Index: Books, 1933 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - University of Texas: General, 1933-1938 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - University of Texas: General, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - University of Texas: Program: Commencement, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Waco: General, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Waco: General, 1936-1942 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Waco: General, 1943-1944, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Waco: General, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Waco: Churches, 1930-1935 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Waco: Churches, 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Waco: Churches, 1941, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Waco: Housing Authority, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Waco: Housing Authority, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Waco: Zoning: General, 1931-1932 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Waco: Zoning: General, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Waco: Zoning: “What Does Our City Need”, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1941 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1942-1944, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Waco Development Company: General, 1943, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Waco Development Company: Court Briefing, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - World War II, 1918-1935 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - World War II, 1936-1940 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - World War II, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - World War II (1 of 2), 1943 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - World War II (2 of 2), 1943 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - World War II, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Politics: General, 1933-1940, undated (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Politics: Election Campaigns, 1935-1941, undated (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Politics: Texas, 1933-1942 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Spanish-American War: Morning War Bulletin, 1898 April-May (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Waco: History, 1923 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 6)
- Collected Materials, 1836-1943, undated; 6; This series contains two document boxes and two oversized boxes.
  This series contains materials collected, not produced, by Kenneth Aynesworth. This series is different from the subject files because the materials are not organized by topic but by type of material. However, the themes of politics, history, education, and medicine are still prominent. The series is in good condition.
  - General, 1836-1894 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - General, 1898-1933 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - General, 1934-1939 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - General (1 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - General (2 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - General (3 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - General (4 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - General (5 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - General (6 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - General (7 of 9), undated (Box 26, Folder 17)